<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Thabo J. van Woudenberg</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Thabo J. van Woudenberg</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Thabo J. van Woudenberg &amp;copy; 2020</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The effect of the weather on adolescents&#39; physical activity.</title>
      <link>/post/weather-on-pa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/weather-on-pa/</guid>
      <description>Hi all!
While I’m a writing this blog, I’m sitting in the train. Soaked… again. It has been raining for quite some weeks now and the weather report doesn’t give me much hope for the next weeks. I certainly don’t want to go outside to train for the half-marathon. To make myself a little less depressed, I think it is time for a new blog.
In this blog, I wanted to see whether I am the only one, or whether the kids in the MyMovez project sample also are less physically active on rainy days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Custom function for Jaccard Index in Igraph</title>
      <link>/post/custom-function-for-jaccard-index-in-igraph/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/custom-function-for-jaccard-index-in-igraph/</guid>
      <description>Hi all!
I while ago, I had the problem that I wanted to compare the edges between two different time points, but also the edges of different types of networks. To be more specific, I wanted to compare:
The edges of the same network between different wavesThe edges in social network based on a nomination question (“With whom do you spend time during the breaks at school”) to the edges based on Bluetooth connects of participants’ smartphonesFor more information, see the protocol paper of the project</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>